<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="63">
    <author>MEMDOR</author>
    <version>1.1.0.0</version>
    <title>
        <en>Boeckmann MH-AL-4320 Auto-Load.</en>
        <de>Boeckmann MH-AL-4320 Auto-Lader.</de>
        <fr>Boeckmann MH-AL-4320 Chargement Automatique.</fr>
        <it>Boeckmann MH-AL-4320 Caricatore Automatico.</it>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en><![CDATA[
Achimobil "Pallet Autoloader Specialization" is required for the Pallet Autoloader function.

Boeckmann MH-AL-4320 car trailer with pallet autoloader function facilitates your work with productions and numerous pallets. 

Up to 12 Euro pallets can be transported with one tour.

Euro pallets, liquid tanks, BigBag pallets, cotton round bales and oversized Euro pallets can be loaded by the pallet autoloader specialization.

The payload can be selected in the store between 6 and 12 Euro pallets. 
Color choice for rims.

Changelog V 1.1.0.0
- Driving behavior at full charge improved.
- Tested with TestRunner_public (GIANTS).
- New store image added
- New icon image added
- Description in modDesc adjusted

Changelog V 1.0.8.0
- Lights problem fixed
    
Changelog V 1.0.7.0
- Color selection rims 
- Logos attached
            ]]></en>
			
        <de><![CDATA[
Für die Funktion des Paletten-Autoloader wird die „Paletten Autoloader Spezialisierung“ von Achimobil benötigt.

Boeckmann MH-AL-4320 Auto-Anhänger mit Paletten-Autoloader Funktion erleichter Ihnen die Arbeit mit den Produktionen und den zahlreichen Paletten. 

Bis zu 12 Euro-Paletten können mit einer Tour transportiert werden.

Euro-Paletten,  Flüssigkeitstanks, BigBag Paletten, Baumwolle Rundballen und übergroße Euro-Paletten können von der Paletten Autoloader Spezialisierung geladen werden.

Die Zuladung kann im Shop zwischen 6 und 12 Euro Paletten gewählt werden. 
Farbwahl für Felgen.

Changelog V 1.1.0.0
- Fahrverhalten bei Vollladung verbessert.
- Getestet mit TestRunner_public (GIANTS).
- Neues Store Bild hinzugefügt
- Neues Icon Bild hinzugefügt
- Beschreibung in der modDesc angepasst

Changelog V 1.0.8.0
- Lichter Problem behoben
    
Changelog V 1.0.7.0
- Farbauswahl Felgen 
- Logos angebracht
            ]]></de>
			
        <fr><![CDATA[
Pour la fonction autochargeur de palettes, la "spécialisation autochargeur de palettes" d'Achimobil est nécessaire.

La remorque auto Boeckmann MH-AL-4320 avec fonction autochargeuse de palettes vous facilite le travail avec les productions et les nombreuses palettes. 

Jusqu'à 12 euro-palettes peuvent être transportées en une seule tournée.

Les palettes Euro, les citernes de liquide, les palettes BigBag, les balles rondes de coton et les palettes Euro surdimensionnées peuvent être chargées par la spécialisation Palettes Autoloader.

La charge utile peut être choisie dans la boutique entre 6 et 12 palettes Euro. 
Choix de la couleur des jantes.

Changelog V 1.1.0.0
- Driving behavior at full charge improved.
- Tested with TestRunner_public (GIANTS).
- Nouvelle image Store ajoutée
- Nouvelle image d'icône ajoutée
- Description adaptée dans le modDesc

Changelog V 1.0.8.0
- Lights problem fixed
    
Changelog V 1.0.7.0
- Color selection rims 
- Logos attached
            ]]></fr>
			
        <it><![CDATA[
La "Specializzazione Pallet Autoloader" di Achimobil è necessaria per la funzione Pallet Autoloader.

Il rimorchio per auto Boeckmann MH-AL-4320 con funzione di caricatore automatico di pallet vi facilita il lavoro con produzioni e numerosi pallet. 

Fino a 12 europallet possono essere trasportati in un solo viaggio.

Gli europallet, i serbatoi di liquidi, i pallet BigBag, le balle rotonde di cotone e gli europallet sovradimensionati possono essere caricati dalla specializzazione del caricatore automatico di pallet.

La capacità di carico può essere selezionata in negozio tra 6 e 12 europallet. 
Scelta del colore dei cerchi.

Changelog V 1.1.0.0
- Comportamento di guida migliorato a piena carica.
- Testato con TestRunner_public (GIANTS).
- Aggiunta una nuova immagine del negozio
- Aggiunta una nuova immagine icona
- Descrizione nel modDesc adattata

Changelog V 1.0.8.0
- Problema delle luci risolto
    
Changelog V 1.0.7.0
- Selezione del colore dei cerchi 
- Loghi allegati
            ]]></it>
    </description>
	
    <iconFilename>icon_mhal4320.png</iconFilename>
	
    <multiplayer supported="true"/>
	
    <storeItems>
        <storeItem xmlFilename="mhal4320.xml"/>
    </storeItems>

    <dependencies>
        <dependency>FS22_aPalletAutoLoader</dependency>
    </dependencies>

    <brands>
        <brand name="MEMDOR" title="MEMDOR" image="brand.icon.dds"/>
    </brands>

    <vehicleTypes>
        <type name="PalletAutoLoaderCarTrailer" parent="trailer" filename="$dataS/scripts/vehicles/Vehicle.lua">
            <specialization name="FS22_aPalletAutoLoader.aPalletAutoLoader"/>
        </type>
    </vehicleTypes>
	
    <l10n filenamePrefix="translat/l10n"/>
	
</modDesc>
